                       Deck ----> Players                      
                       Initial Hand                      
player: this is what I have in my hand...4 9  Your total value is: 13
dealer: this is what I have in my hand...10 3  Your total value is: 13


                       Deck ----> Players                      
                         Final Hand                      
player: this is what I have in my hand...4 9 3  Your total value is: 16
dealer: this is what I have in my hand...10 3 3 5  Your total value is: 21
                         It's a Tie!!!                     
0
                       Deck ----> Players                      
                       Initial Hand                      
player: this is what I have in my hand...10 10  Your total value is: 20
dealer: this is what I have in my hand...10 4  Your total value is: 14


                       Deck ----> Players                      
                         Final Hand                      
player: this is what I have in my hand...10 10  Your total value is: 20
dealer: this is what I have in my hand...10 4 8  Your total value is: 22
                      Player Won!!!                      
1
                       Deck ----> Players                      
                       Initial Hand                      
player: this is what I have in my hand...3 2  Your total value is: 5
dealer: this is what I have in my hand...10 4  Your total value is: 14


                       Deck ----> Players                      
                         Final Hand                      
player: this is what I have in my hand...3 2 2 7 6  Your total value is: 20
dealer: this is what I have in my hand...10 4 10  Your total value is: 24
                      Player Won!!!                      
1
